A Guide to the National Committee on United States-China Relations records, RG 6, Accession 6 FA1188
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Development, 1968-2009; 10
  - Proposals to the United States Information Agency (Projects on American Federalism and Chinese Local Elected Officials), 1995 (Box 23, Folder 210-211)
    RFP, Local Government Grant Competition. Proposals submitted March 1995.
  - Proposal to the United States Information Agency for FY 1996 (Grant IA-PSMA-G6190061), 1995 September (Box 23, Folder 212)
    File includes proposal and attachments. Revised versions of the proposal are found in the grant correspondence files.
  - United States Information Agency: Grant for FY 1996 (IA-PSMA-G6190061, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Folder 213)
    File includes various revised versions of the proposal and budgets, along with grant correspondence.
  - United States Information Agency: Grant for FY 1996 (IA-PSMA-G6190061, 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 214-216)
  - Final Report to the United States Information Agency on Grant IA-PSMA-G6190061, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 217)
  - United States Information Agency: Congressional Inquiry, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 218-219)
    Inquiry into USIA grant funding for National Committee programs.
  - Proposal to the United States Information Agency (Role of Individuals in Environmental Protection), 1995 October (Box 24, Folder 220)
    RFP grant IA-PSCF-G6190125.
  - United States Information Agency: Grant IA-PSCF-G6190125 (Role of Individuals in Environmental Protection), 1995-1998 (Box 24, Folder 221)
  - Proposal to the United States Information Agency for FY 1997, 1996 October (Box 25, Folder 222)
    Grant IA-PSPS-G7190069
  - United States Information Agency: Grant for FY 1997 (IA-PSPS-G7190069), 1996-2001 (Box 25, Folder 223)
  - Final Report to the United States Information Agency on Grant IA-PSPS-G7190069, 2000 (Box 25, Folder 224)
  - United States Information Agency: Grant IA-PSLJ-G7190077 (Regional Broadcasting Project), 1996-2000 (Box 25, Folder 225)
  - Final Report to the United States Information Agency on Grant IA-PSLJ-G7190077 (Regional Broadcasting Project), 2000 (Box 25, Folder 226)
  - United States Information Agency: Grant IA-PLMA-G7190155 (FY 1997, Taiwan Local Leaders Delegation), 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 227)
    RFP grant, Local-Level Governance project for Taiwan Officials.
  - United States Information Agency: Minister of Justice Delegation, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 228)
    Budget and expenditure information on Visit of Minister of Justice Xiao Yang, 1997 November 14-20. Materials were filed with other U. S. Information Agency files, but it is not clear who funded the delegation visit. It was not part of the FY 1997 authorization, but it may have been included among FY 1998 allocations.
  - Proposal to the United States Information Agency Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs for FY 1998 (Box 25, Folder 229)
    Reference number E/P-98-11.
  - United States Information Agency: Grant for FY 1998 (IA-PSMA-G8190048), 1997-2002 (Box 26, Folder 230-231)
    Correspondence concerning proposal and grant agreements.
  - Proposal to the United States Information Agency Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Court Specialization and Civil Trial Procedure Project), 1998 September 30 (Box 26, Folder 232)
    Proposal for FY 1999. Reference number E/P-99-1.
  - Proposal to the United States Information Agency Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs for FY 1999, 1998 October (Box 26, Folder 233)
    Reference number E/P-99-16.
  - United States Information Agency and U. S. Department of State: Grant for FY 1999 ( IA-PLMA-G9190041) (Correspondence), 1998-2002 (Box 26, Folder 234-235)
  - Report to the U. S. Department of State on Grants IA-PSMA-G8190048 and IA-PLMA-G9190041, 1998-2002, 2004 (Box 26, Folder 236-237)
    Exchange programs, FY 1998 and FY 1999.
  - United States Information Agency: Congressional Inquiry, 1999 (Box 27, Folder 238)
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Worker Retraining), 1999 October 12 (Box 27, Folder 239)
    Reference number E/P-00-1.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (New Channels for Private Philanthropy in China), 1999 October 13 (Box 27, Folder 240)
  - Final Report to the United States Department of Education on Contract ED-99-CO-0101, 1999-2001 (Box 27, Folder 241)
    Fulbright-Hays Seminars Abroad Program and Exchange Activities with China.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs for FY 2000 (Box 27, Folder 242)
  - U. S. Department of State: FY 2000 Grant Proposal and Correspondence (PEMA-1052), 1999-2002 (Box 27, Folder 243)
  - U. S. Department of State: Grant Correspondence, FY 2000- FY 2001 (Box 27, Folder 244)
    Includes materials on Grant PEMA-1052.
  - Final Report to the U. S. Department of State on Grant PEMA 1052, 2001-2002, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 245)
    Grant Agreement PEMA-1052 (2001 January - 2002 June). File consists mainly of delegation itineraries and trip reports.
  - U. S. Department of State: Congressional Inquiry FY 2000 Grants, 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 246-247)
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Court Specialization/ Alternative Dispute Resolution), 2000 October 25 (Box 28, Folder 248)
    Reference number E/P-01-1. Grant declined.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (NGO Development), 2000 October 25 (Box 28, Folder 249)
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs for FY 2001, 2000 October (Box 28, Folder 250)
  - U. S. Department of State: Fiscal Year 2001 Grant Correspondence and Budgeting, 2000-2002 (Box 28, Folder 251)
    Grant S-ECAPE-02-GR-065.
  - Report to the U. S. Department of State on Grant ECAPE-02-GR-065, 2002, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 252)
    Final report sent 2006 for WTO Workshop to China, 2002 October 18-27, Democracy and Elections Project in the U. S., 2002 October 30 - November 9, Municipal Finance and Environmental Infrastructure Study Tour to China, 2002 November 30 - December 11, Economic Development and Environment Management Delegation from China, 2002 June 22 - July 5.
  - Application to the United States Department of Education, 1999 December (Box 28, Folder 253)
    RFP ED-00-R-0002. Technical and Business Proposals and Past Performance Report.
  - Application to the United States Department of Education, 2000 March (Box 28, Folder 254)
    RFP ED-00-R-0002. Proposal for contract to administer Fulbright-Hays Summer Seminar to China and visits each year of two delegations of Chinese educators, for period FY 2001 - FY 2005.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs for FY 2002 (Box 29, Folder 255)
    Proposal for an assistance award of $362,000, submitted October 11, 2001. Reference number ECA/PE/C-02-09.
  - U. S. Department of State: Fiscal Year 2002 Grant Correspondence, 2001-2004 (Box 29, Folder 256-257)
    Assistance Award S-ECAPE-02-GR-246 (Proposal reference number ECA/PE/C-02-09).
  - U. S. Department of State: Fiscal Year 2002 Proposal Financial Correspondence, 2001-2005 (Box 29, Folder 258)
    Agreement S-ECAPE-02-GR-246.
  - Final Report to the U.S. Department of State on Grant Agreement S-ECAPE-02-GR-246, 2003-2005 (Box 29, Folder 259)
    For Sino-American exchange projects focusing on anti-corruption, anti-money laundering, HIV/AIDS, and worker retraining. (See Proposal, FY 2002.)
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Tibet Vocational Education), 2002 June 12 (Box 29, Folder 260)
    Proposal to develop/implement a two-way exchange between American and Tibetan experts and practitioners in the fields of vocational education and entrepreneurship development. Reference number ECA/PE/C/WHAEAP-02-66.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Worker Displacement in China), 2002 October 2 (Box 29, Folder 261)
    Proposal for a project on developing innovative policies to address worker displacement issues in China. Reference number ECA/PE/C-03-01.
  - U. S. Department of State: RFP Grant (Correspondence and Budgeting) (Worker Displacement in China), 2002-2006 (Box 29, Folder 262)
    Grant S-ECAPE-03-GR-098.
  - Report to the U. S. Department of State on Grant Agreement S-ECAPE-03-GR-098, 2003-2006 (Box 29, Folder 263)
    Worker Displacement Program in the U. S. and China.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Developing Volunteerism in China), 2002 October 2 (Box 30, Folder 264)
    Proposal to develop/implement a two-way exchange between American and Chinese experts and practitioners on developing and strengthening volunteerism in China. Reference number ECA/PE/C-03-01.
  - U. S. Department of State: RFP Grant (Correspondence and Budgeting) (Developing Volunteerism in China), 2002-2007 (Box 30, Folder 265)
    Grant S-ECAPE-03-GR-117.
  - Report to the U. S. Department of State on Grant Agreement S-ECAPE-03-GR-117, 2003-2007 (Box 30, Folder 266)
    Programs in China and the U.S. in 2005-2006 on Strengthening Volunteer Management in Chinese NGOs. Interim and Final Reports.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (WTO Workshop II: Agricultural Biotechnology), 2002 October 2 (Box 30, Folder 267)
    Reference number ECA/PE/C-03-01.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Strengthening the Work of Legal Aid Centers in China), 2002 October 2 (Box 30, Folder 268)
  - U. S. Department of State: Grant Correspondence, FY 2003 (Box 30, Folder 269)
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Entrepreneurship Education for Tibetan Youth), 2003 May 29 (Box 30, Folder 270)
    Proposal to develop/implement a two-way exchange between American and Tibetan educators to strengthen and expand entrepreneurial training for youth in the Tibet Autonomous Region. Reference number ECA/PE/C/WHAEAP-03-48
  - U. S. Department of State: Popular Legal Education and Tibet Proposals, 2003 June (Box 30, Folder 271)
    Proposals for projects on Popular Legal Education and Expanding Opportunities for Tibetans, in response to a RFP from the Bureau of Democracy, Human Rights and Labor. File mainly concerns budgeting.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Promoting Open Markets in Agricultural Biotechnology Trade), 2003 October 2 (Box 30, Folder 272)
    Reference number ECA/PE/C-04-01.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Developing Effective Media Campaigns for HIV/AIDS Education in China), 2003 October 2 (Box 30, Folder 273)
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Community Planning for HIV/AIDS Prevention and Treatment in China), 2003 October 2 (Box 31, Folder 274)
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Enhancing Measures to Fight Counterfeiting ), 2003 October 2 (Box 31, Folder 275)
  - U. S. Department of State: Fiscal Year 2004 RFP Grant Correspondence, 2003-2006 (Box 31, Folder 276-277)
    Grants S-ECAPE-04-GR-134 (HIV /AIDS Education Media Campaigns) and S-ECAPE-04-GR-137 (HIV/AIDS Community Planning). File also concerns unsuccessful proposals for programs on Agricultural Biotechnology and Measures to Fight Counterfeiting.
  - Report to the United States Department of State on Grant Agreement S-ECAPE-04-GR-134, 2007 (Box 31, Folder 278)
    Program on Developing Effective Media Campaigns for HIV/AIDS in the U. S. and China, 2004-2006.
  - Report to the United States Department of State on Grant Agreement S-ECAPE-04-GR-137, 2006 (Box 31, Folder 279)
    HIV/AIDS Community Planning Program in the U.S. and China, 2004-2006.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Democracy, Human Rights and Labor (Advancing Religious Freedom in China), 2004 April 28 (Box 31, Folder 280)
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Democracy, Human Rights and Labor (Raising Legal Awareness in China), 2004 April 28 (Box 31, Folder 281)
    Project on Raising Legal Awareness in the People's Republic of China through Popular Culture.
  - Proposals to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Democracy, Human Rights and Labor (Correspondence and Budgets), 2004 April (Box 31, Folder 282)
    File mainly concerns budgeting for three proposals (all declined): Advancing Religious Freedom in China, Federalism and Democracy in China, and Raising Legal Awareness through Popular Culture.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Strengthening Anti-Corruption Practices in China's Civil Service), 2004 November 18 (Box 31, Folder 283)
    Reference number ECA/PE/C-05-01.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Improving Government Response to Chinese Workers' Questions and Concerns), 2004 November 18 (Box 31, Folder 284)
  - Final Program Report to the U.S. Department of Education for 2004 (Box 32, Folder 285)
    Report dated 2005 February 8.
  - Proposal to the U. S. Department of State Bureau of Educational and Cultural Affairs (Teachers of Critical Languages Program), 2006 April 14 (Box 32, Folder 286)
    Program to strengthen teaching of critical languages, including Mandarin Chinese and Arabic, in American K-12 schools.
  - U. S. Department of Education, 1987-2000 (Box 41, Folder 356-359)
    Contracts, budgets, and correspondence concerning funding for Fulbright exchange programs. Includes list of Department of Education funding from 1980-1987.
  - U. S. Department of Education, 1999-2000 (Box 42, Folder 360)
    RFP ED-00-R-0002. Solicitation correspondence and forms concerning multiyear contract for FY2001 - FY 2005 to administer Fulbright-Hays Summer Seminar in China and Education delegations to U. S.
  - U. S. Department of Education - Reimbursements, 1999-2001 (Box 42, Folder 361)
  - U. S. Department of Education - Contracts and Reimbursements, 2001-2003 (Box 42, Folder 362)
  - U. S. Department of Education FY 2003 Contract, 2003-2005 (Box 42, Folder 363)
  - U. S. Department of Education - Reimbursements, 2004-2005 (Box 42, Folder 364)
  - U. S. Department of Education - Reimbursements, 2006-2007 (Box 42, Folder 365)
  - U. S. Department of Labor: U. S. - China Labor Law Cooperation Project (General), 2002-2007 (Box 42, Folder 366-367)
    Also described as the China Labor Rule of Law program. Correspondence, Timelines and Progress Reports, Budgets, Financial Long Forms. The Department of Labor funded this project in a cooperative agreement with Worldwide Strategies Inc. and subcontractors the Asia Foundation and the NCUSCR.
  - U. S. Department of Labor: U. S. - China Labor Law Cooperation Project (Contracts), 2002-2003 (Box 43, Folder 368-369)
    The Department of Labor funded this project in a cooperative agreement with Worldwide Strategies Inc. and subcontractors the Asia Foundation and the NCUSCR.
  - Proposals to the U. S. Department of State, Bureau of Democracy, Human Rights, and Labor for FY 2005, 2005 April (Box 43, Folder 370)
    Projects on Increasing Public Participation in Land Use Decisions, and Using the Media to Promote Legal Awareness.
  - U. S. Department of State: Grant for U. S. - China Cultural Industry Policy Forum, 2006 (Box 43, Folder 371)
    Grant award no. S-CH500-06-GR-115. Forum held in New York on September 13, 2006.
  - United States Information Agency: Congressional Inquiry, 1998 (Box 43, Folder 372)
  - Albert Kunstadter Family Foundation, 2002 (Box 43, Folder 373)
  - Andrew W. Mellon Foundation, 1968-1979, 1982 (Box 43, Folder 374)
  - Asia Foundation, 1994 (Box 43, Folder 375)
  - Eurasia Foundation, 1994-1995 (Box 43, Folder 376)
  - Henry Luce Foundation, 1979-1995 (Box 43, Folder 377-378)
    Includes draft of trip report of study group on Greater China and Sino - U. S. Economic Relations, March 17-24, 1992. Luce Foundation officer Terrill Lautz was one of the participants.
  - Report to the Henry Luce Foundation on the Civil Society Project in China (1999) (Box 44, Folder 379)
  - Howard Gilman Foundation, 1990, 1996-1999 (Box 44, Folder 380)
  - John D. and Catherine T. MacArthur Foundation, 1987-1993, 2006-2007 (Box 44, Folder 381-383)
  - John Holdridge Memorial Fund, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 384)
  - Kettering Foundation, 1980-1997 (Box 44, Folder 385)
  - Lingnan Foundation, 2000-2001 (Box 44, Folder 386)
    Grant in support of a delegation from the Chinese Research Center for Teaching and Learning in Universities and Colleges, the visit never took place.
  - Maclellan Foundation, 2005 (Box 44, Folder 387)
  - New York Community Trust, 2007 (Box 44, Folder 388)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1979-1988 (Box 44, Folder 389)
  - Rockefeller Brothers Fund, 1989-1997 (Box 45, Folder 390)
  - Smith Richardson Foundation, 1999-2000 (Box 45, Folder 391)
    Support for Airlie Conference on the Future of U. S. - China Relations and for Conference on Challenges and Opportunities in the Taiwan Strait.
  - Smith Richardson Foundation (Grants to Individuals), 1999-2002, 2009 (Box 45, Folder 392)
  - Tibet Poverty Alleviation Fund, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 393)
    Reimbursement of surplus funds designated for the Tibet Vocational Education Delegation. File also references a Tibet Community College Project.
  - Time Warner Internship Program (Financial Reporting), 2001-2006 (Box 45, Folder 394)
  - Trust for Mutual Understanding, 1993-1998 (Box 45, Folder 395)
    Support for the Ussuri River Watershed Project.
  - U. S. - China Education Foundation (Community College Leadership Delegation), 2001 (Box 45, Folder 396)
  - U. S. - China Legal Cooperation Fund, 2003 (Box 45, Folder 397)
    Support for project on Strengthening the Work of Legal Aid Centers in China. The Legal Cooperation Fund is a program of the U. S. - China Business Council.
  - United Technologies Corporation, 2000-2002 (Box 45, Folder 398)
    Support for 2001 Grassroots Environmentalism Workshop in China.
  - Weeden Foundation, 1993-1998 (Box 45, Folder 399)
  - Ussuri River Watershed Project, 1993-1995 (Box 45, Folder 400-401)
    File mainly concerns budgeting and financial reporting. Project funders included the Asia Foundation, Eurasia Foundation, MacArthur Foundation, Rockefeller Brothers Fund, and Weeden Foundation.
  - Ussuri River Watershed Project, 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 402)
  - May Lee Industries (David Buxbaum), circa 1973 (Box 49, Folder 448)
    Promotional brochures and press releases for company engaged in trade with China. Buxbaum was president and chair.
  - Separated Oversized Material (Box 50)
    Oversized material separated from Series 10, box 21, folder 194; and from Series 11, box 4, folder 43.
- Board of Directors, Committees, and Members records, 1966-2006; 11
  The Board, Committees, Members series in RG 6 contains membership and committee records from 1966 to the mid-2000s. Membership materials concern nominations and recruitment and include lists of members by region and occupation, plus a run of Member Mailings files from 1966 to 2005. Records for various committees established in the late 1960s – early 1970s (Development, Education, Exchanges, Program Review, Fact-Finding, Finance, etc.), while spotty, provide some insight into the National Committee's early organizational history. Executive Committee Meetings and Mailings records, 1967-2003, and a Minutes Book (for the Board and Executive Committee), 1966-1975, also provide a more comprehensive picture of the National Committee's decisions and activities. Committee records and minutes in this series notably document the National Committee's decision in the mid-1970s to prioritize its cultural and educational exchange activities and to spin off its education program
  - Membership Invitation Letter, 1966 April, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Organizing Group invitation to form a National Committee on U. S. - China Relations. Two versions of the letter.
  - Board of Directors: Officers and Members Lists, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Memos to the Board and Executive Committee, 1971, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Policy Paper on Future Directions, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Douglas Murray paper, "A Mission for the National Committee on U. S. - China Relations," 1984 October 29. Mailing, 1984 November 2.
  - Development Committee, 1966, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
  - Education Committee Meeting and Mailings, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Exchanges Committee, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Program Review Committee Meeting, 1973 February 5 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Fact Finding Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    The Fact Finding Committee was tasked with helping the National Committee implement its reorganization toward educational and cultural exchanges and Policy Studies, and in the termination of its general educational programs.
  - Finance Committee, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising: General, 1972 June (Box 1, Folder 12)
    A. Doak Barnett Letters, June 16, Letter to various corporations (Arne's List), June 30, Letters to corporations who attended Canton Fair, June 30.
  - Fundraising: Financial Contributions to Table Tennis Project, 1970 October-1972 September (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Contributions for FY 1970-1971 and FY 1971-1972.
  - Fundraising: Mailing to Previous Table Tennis Contributors, 1972 May 29 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising: Acknowledgments of Table Tennis Contributions Received between May 3 and June 15, 1972, 1972 June (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Fundraising: Mailing to Fund for Peace List, 1972 June 9 (Box 2, Folder 16)
    Seeking funds to cover Table Tennis Project deficit.
  - Publications Review Board Mailing, 1968 July 23 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    1 item.
  - Symposia Subcommittee Meeting, 1968 August 21 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    Mailing to Alexander Eckstein, Lucien Pye, and Carl F. Stover, August 21.
  - Membership: General, 1969-1973 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    Invitations and procedures.
  - Member Services, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Membership: Alphabetical List, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Membership: Lists by Region and Occupation, 1967, 1970-1976 (Box 2, Folder 22-23)
    Includes Mailing List, circa 1970-1971, which was divided by region and within regions by occupation. These divisions were numbered sequentially, and the numbers then served in some cases as a category code for targeted mailings or in other ways as a descriptive tag.
  - Membership: Breakdown by State, 1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Membership: Address List, 1967-1970 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Membership: Invitation Letters (Samples), 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Membership: Welcome Letter to New Members, 1966-1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Membership: Suggestions, 1977-1979 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Membership: Invitations, 1976 August-1977 August (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Membership: Invitations, 1978 August (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Membership: Nominations, 1982 Fall (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Membership Nominating Committee, 1969-1977 (Box 3, Folder 32-36)
  - Membership Nominating Committee, 1988-1996 (Box 3, Folder 37-38)
    File includes copy of the National Committee's Bylaws.
  - Mailing on the Cultural Revolution and Replies, 1967 November 7-14 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    Mailing enclosing articles and journalists' accounts, members mailing included NCUSCR program summary, May-October 1967.
  - Mailing on China and the United Nations and Replies, 1967 November 20 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Mailing to New Senators, 1969 February (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Congressional Mailing, 1969 February 27 (Box 4, Folder 42)